IJEOMA AMARA OJUKWU

ojukwuijeomaamara@gmail.com +2348060646993

Mararaba, Karu LGA, Nasarawa State

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

A goal oriented and dedicated Customer Support personnel with more than 5 years practical experience in handling customer needs. Possesses a great ability to identify and understand customers thereby resulting in the growth of a company. Carrying out occasional surveys to quantify and measure the customer's retention and growth.

SKILLS

- Able to understand the needs of individual customers and meet them.
- An ability to work without supervision and yet deliver outstanding results.
- A highly coordinated individual who works effectively with teams.
- An ability to pay close attention to details.
- Possesses great understanding of CRM tools.
- Understands how to effectively communicate with the English Language.

TOOLS

Microsoft Suite, Canva, MySQL, Google Workspace, Github, Cloud Services, Office 356, Power BI, Google Suite, React, Zendesk, Live Chat, Buffer, Outlook, Salesforce

WORK EXPERIENCE

Customer Support/ Representative

July 2023 – Till date

First Kingdom Kids Academy

- Dealing with general telephone enquiries, taking messages accurately, giving information and advice to staff, parents and pupils.
- Sorting and resolving all technical issues related to the software application.
- Reporting and analysing all product malfunctions and ensuring it is resolved immediately.
- Monitoring database entries and updating parents on the new features.
- Acting as the first point of contact between the customers and the school.

Customer Support Representative

June 2019 – July 2023

Nnamdi Azikiwe University (IT Department)

- Provided timely and effective support for the students experiencing technical issues with the servers.
- Attended promptly to the inquiries of the students via phone, emails and live chat.
- Taught 100+ students on the practical application and use cases of programming languages.
- Documented all feedback given by the students noting areas that required urgent attention.
- Measured team progress on a daily and weekly basis thereby offering improved services to students.

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

Teacher August 2018 - June 2019

DimConnect, Uli

- Actively involved in the training of 500+ women in Tech Skills.
- Designed training materials used during the duration of the session.
- Counselled women on the importance of acquiring tech skills in the 21st Century.

Member May 2015 - April 2016

NYSC (Road Safety Club), Toto, Bauchi

- Participated in awareness campaigns on proper road safety ethics
- Collaborated with local road safety agencies to put up traffic signs in the community.
- Joined in educating community members on the importance of abiding to road rules.

Assistant Corps Members Liaison Officer

May 2015 - April 2016

Office of The Local Government Inspector, Toro LGA, Bauchi

- Coordinated and organised the activities of the organisation.
- Drafted and wrote down the reports of the meetings.
- Keep the office clean and tidy.

EDUCATION

Chukwuemeka Odumegwu Ojukwu University, Uli, Anambra

2023

Masters of Science in Computer Science (MSc Computer)

Chukwuemeka Odumegwu Ojukwu University, Uli, Anambra

2014

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science (Bsc Computer)

REFEREES

Available on Request